From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringing love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like we awake and step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like we awake and don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream live from the madness, this ain't no dream
scare you the tr-
Hello guys, came by one more time, hi babe, see Lola looking at Lola's eyes, some big
eyes huh, hi guys, I just had a nice shower, hi what's up, there we go, hello, let's see,
Where are my glasses?
Hi everybody, how are you tonight? Hi VB
Yeah, my ears are like all clogged right now. Oh
I mean having these like these headphones in and then like
Hi Lola Lola's in front of the camera. I have a I have a burger like heating up the fridge
Hi Lola
You're in the way. You're in the way
All right, come on. I'm gonna grab my drink man burger one second
Okay
Okay guys
How are we tonight
We'll do another free we'll do another short show free night. Yeah. Thank you, bb. Hi, dg. Electra. How are you?
Hi, Lola's over here. Hi Lola. I got a couple new decks today guys. I got this really cool deck called
This one is called Believe in your own magic.
Believe in your own magic. So, I'll pull a few for the chat.
These are, like I said, easier to shuffle. I like the...
These Timu cards are like feel good in the hand. They're like the right texture.
They're even though they're a little bit thinner, they're just easier to shuffle and easier to handle.
You don't always need the most expensive card stock.
Because these just like feel right in my hands. Okay, so what do we got?
You're stoned. I'm almost there. We have tree. It says let them go. Maybe it's time to let go of somebody
If there's a tree there is that and she's a she's still mourning, you know, but maybe
It's time to let someone go. Okay
What else we got we have thorns it says work together
Let's see work weave together
the crown you deserve.
Weave together the crown you deserve.
Okay, what else do we got?
Finally, for the chat, we have
we have a villain.
You can always rewrite the story.
Uh-oh.
She's this woman.
She's about to crush that.
So she's kind of the villain,
but she can always rewrite.
Hey, Flirty Diamonds, how are you?
You can always rewrite the story.
Those meant anything to you. Hope they did. How are you guys? Uh-oh. Here's Rudy too. Hey Rudy. Uh-oh
Are you yelling at Rudy?
Rudy likes to light. Hi
There we go, you can always rewrite the story. Hey, rude. Hi, rude
Rude's back here. Hi everybody. How are you? How is your uh? Yeah, I got another another deck called this one's called the uh?
Celestial carnival. It's really pretty colors
Hope Celestial carnival and I have some cards for there too. I'll do it a little bit
Yeah, I know no look at there's Rudy of Rudy's right here here
Rudy
Hi guys
Yeah, so I vacuumed up real good. I got a new vacuum. There's only
Cats are fighting. There's only 20 something bucks. I also got this I have a I have a vape
But I'm afraid to hit it, but uh
I'll go ahead and hit the vape. Yeah, Lenore. Lenore's been inside. She was inside. I think she's outside right now
She's been here. Jamie give me always words about Lenore, but Lenore's been spending a lot of time outside lately
Yeah, kiddies are fighting and then Rudy is watching he's up there watching the door. He's watching the door right there
tricks around
Hi guys proof of life. Oh, Jamie. I've done that several times Jamie
How many times have you asked about Lenore and I've shown Lenore many several times? So don't worry. He's just fine. I promise you
JV what do you think you think I would you think I would not tell the chat if something happened, you know come on
Give me a little credit. I'll be right back
Oh
Okay, so yeah, did you hope you guys saw earlier?
I had Daddy Bigness in today, or it was Andrew,
but he was really a great guest.
Unfortunately, I got foreign bombed a few times.
So I'm gonna try to put his interview back up
if I can't accept to edit out the foreign bomb part.
And I started, I mean,
I wish you would come back in more often.
Hey, Trix, I wish you would come back in more often.
I think that, you know, there are four cats in here
all the time and she gets a little bit jealous sometimes,
I don't know. I hope she comes back in more often. Hi guys
Yeah, so nice to see you guys. Hope you had a good night, and I would that I'd be the came in earlier was pretty
Interesting she would have been friendly one time. I would have like maybe like answer her, but
All she could say was biscuit it seems like and so
I don't feel like responding to trolling
Anyway
Hi, Trix, want to come up?
Hi.
I don't go, I don't troll in people's chat. I mean, you know, maybe a few I do, but not hers.
It's not too hard to edit stuff out. It just takes a sec.
Yeah, I I deleted it up of YouTube just because I know people have gotten in trouble
We're just even having it in the private and like a porn bomb in the private
And it's like it makes me think of all the privates I have with porn bombs in them
You know because especially when I started so I might have to like go back and
through some of my my old lives and delete them and stuff. I don't know it's like
Hopefully I've
You know, I've deleted a lot of them or
It's only I don't know. I just like hopefully the AI doesn't go through all my videos and
See anything because
It was not
Really my fault
Streamyard is a collects the last 50 hours of shows and so I still have it in my stream yard the complete show
I can try to figure out there how to take it off there and put it on
On YouTube again. It was a good interview. He was really nice
It was nice to have like somebody I'm a fan of like coming up say hi in the chat. He's a he was a he's a power lifter
Guy and he liked the show I think he had fun and he says he's gonna come maybe tomorrow. So that'd be that'd be cool
Thank you, Electra
Hopefully you're good Electra. Good to see ya. Thank you for redoing your membership, too. That really means a lot to me
Yeah, I mean I'm giving away a lot of memberships this month, but I do hope that people enjoy them because
There is I put every video behind the the member wall, right? Hey, what's up? Nobody? How are you?
So every video everything almost every video can you get unblocked now? Yeah, you're not you're not you're not blocked right now Canada dry
You're welcome up
Your
Your blocks are expired
for now haha yeah yeah but uh yeah it is awesome you know thank you i'm doing
good i'm really really good i'm also i'm on a tick talk now if you if you go see
my tick talk i do like a lot more readings because it's like kind of faster
pace over there
And it's like I'm doing pretty well like you know people who give little gifts and stuff like that and some people have given me like little gifts
It's not not very much, but I've already monetized there, too. I already have my membership available there
You know, it's the same price is here. I'm gonna try to keep it like have a lot of value in it
With the you know, I'll do the long readings for the people in that the membership and stuff
There's also private private board like there is here. Yeah
So it took the three days to get monetized on TikTok and so if you guys are looking for like a fast way to get
You know a social media presence like that's probably a pretty good way
If you sell anything like have a store if you have an eBay store you can actually put your stuff on
I don't know if it's like you can put like you stuff
But you can put your stuff onto a TikTok and sell it and they have a TikTok shop
There's a little too too much for me to
And I changed my name to shop it says you're blocked. Okay. I'll block you hold on
Yeah, I must have blocked you the other night accidentally hold on guess
Well, what's it? What was your name? Okay, was it Roger Klotz Rudolph hosts
Merceau Nana
Mondo Garmento. Oh, that was a fake Alex McQueen
Daniel Larson, what was your name?
This monkey's live. Oh shit
I forgot that she was going live. It was none of those.
Yeah, it's Spunky. Go say hi to Spunky. I'm so sorry. I forgot her.
I mean, please post her channel mods and everyone go over there.
Okay, so I'll read the names again to you because it has to be one of these names.
User, Unik 0D3,
Mer-Sol, Mondo Garmento, Nugget Service,
Roger Klotz, Na-Na, Daniel Larson, R.N. or John Wu.
Na-Na, okay.
Those are all porn bombers, by the way.
Okay, I took off Na-Na.
So you should be able to go up now.
Everyone go say hi to Spunky. I think it's what is her channel guys? I forgot her channel's name
Something Spunky something go over there say psyche awakens and sends senses love good luck on her first show
I'm sorry. I forgot that her going live. I didn't mean to compete or anything
Maybe I'll get off in a few minutes. She's still on it. We can go
over there
Hmm, anybody know I think it was a cute name. It was something spunky
Or if you see you're online, just let me know
Okay
Hello yo, you're here
Until someone pays to take me off. I am here. Yeah, so I don't see
I don't see the person in the chat, so I think you're okay for the time being
But how are you doing making money? So thank you. Yeah, I am I am it's like a little bit
It's really awesome because you know, I otherwise I'd be pretty stressed this week, but
Luckily, you know, I have a little
little extra and so I'm doing okay and
Yeah, so how have you been? Thank you for being a good sport about it. By the way, I appreciate that
You know, it's it's really fun. It's funny to me that someone's
Someone's that committed to it
Yeah, I was kind of surprised I was a little bit surprised, but you know, it's like the people that
I'm sure I get under people's skin, too. You know, I think I think this might you know start
I think other people might start doing this too, and it'll be interesting to see who really
is going to get kicked a lot, but I don't know, you're okay, I'm over our little spat
or whatever.
I'm generally pretty chill.
Sometimes things piss me off and I go off the handle, but mostly I just like to chill.
Yeah, I've been probably a little bit oversensitive a little bit recently. It's just uh
Oh you having a nice bar here? I have a I have a vape
Okay, we have Sam and on the show. That's what I noticed you bought a bomb
That was that I
Want to come back. I knew you come back at CD always come back. Yo see check it out see say
I didn't know this motherfucker. He was talking a lot of shit about you
I said, yo, just leave psych alone
Or do you give a fuck what psych do on his channel when it's psych shit and I said I'll bet you
You're gonna come back and look who he is right back. Yeah, right
I told you that right didn't I tell you that you're a weird dude
I mean, I've heard him like I mean, I know if he's gone on shows like and said stuff
I'm like
Complained about you and I told I even told beta this thing is complaining about psych ain't psych is naming it
What up, nobody? What up, Jamie? Um, cowboys
Where they DJ Electra? I'm just saying I'm gonna call it out
Try to stay off of like other shows like you know and stuff like that
But I don't you say you do what you want to do with your shows. I've been told you that I laid off that shit
But what I'm saying niggas is calling you out and they come right back here either environment
You are the corniest black man. I have never come across in my life. Just so you know, I love you too. God bless you
You're like a little fake. You're a little woman of a black man. I'm calling you out. Did you get that?
You know, he was saying to I did so much for psych. I did such a size. I did this and he treats me like this
I don't like you sound like a bitch
Well, you know sask has been like he's been clapped for like two days, you know someone paid $25
It'd be all right. It's a clap. What the fuck people are bitching about psych
I mean was he mad about the past two days he was saying this because he seemed like he was in a good mood
Oh
Again, I'm getting a report like says, you know, you you come here real nice to me and stuff
I know I saw a little bit of her panel last night, and then you know, I was actually
I saw no wonder I see why people clap you off the panel you complain too much
But no reason. That's why he's quiet though. You could talk, I'll mute myself.
No, I'm quiet because you're so fucking annoying. And anytime I talk, you just interrupt me. I can't even speak.
You're annoying as fuck. Go... I don't know, like, maybe you weren't bullied enough by your older brother or something growing up. This is fucking weird, bro.
Leave me the fuck alone, you weirdo.
Okay, well he I'm new to myself site. I'm waiting till he tells me I'm lying about something
Yeah, I'm sure it's the truth, but I mean, I'm a forgiving person. I know people will like be it sometimes
Cook that up, you know that right I could get the live right now and give it right to you. So yeah, yeah
I know I even was able to get that like the live where he was on let me see he was on some show
I think beat his show like, you know saying it's some really bad shit, but you know
I'm just saying if they go fucking hate you for a reason why
and then come back to you. Don't fucking say nothing at all.
Yo, I keep up here to chat, not talk with this weird fuck.
You know, Canada dropped. One thing about me, oh, he left.
Oh, he left? Uh-oh.
See, the two first, y'all. I'm just saying, see?
In the link. I'll get the link.
And I'm not, and it's like, I don't protect you.
I know.
You always sound like it is you always you're whatever you feel if you're honest, you know, I know you come up
You've come up here and tell me oh, you know
I'm gonna call it how I see it
Yeah, I've always you always been honest. I do appreciate that. I mean, it's like I do like hear about
People being too faced sometimes that I never never never you but yeah some like
I could leave it. I mean, I know he just left he left on his own easy's here easy wants to say hi
I
Everybody talk shit about everybody
Niggas make it a whole segment
wasn't it you last night at betas who I'm pretty sure if you want to like really get into this
Like really keep your mouth shut and let me talk for a minute
Okay, I'm pretty sure what it was bro was that I
Me and beta were talking about how I was upset that I wasn't on panel yada yada yada, ba ba ba
No, you know, no, can I talk for a sec? You was not beta
Both of us were no be the wasn't live. We didn't know nothing until you was up there
You complain was live. I was on her live panel. Are you know be the was live you got caught off-site shit
You should stop talking cuz you don't sound smart, okay, I'm not smart, but you a bitch ass nigga
I can't stand already. Just catch I know this man
There's always a clip at his ship at moment, all right?
No matter what you say.
No, I ain't gonna hold you, Canada.
JT, not around.
Fuck Gotti.
You my new target over here, nigga.
Word, bro.
I am gonna hold you.
I was over at betas and we were talking about how I was kicked, blah, blah, blah, and came up talking about how I was crying about it.
And why would I cry about it?
Because he doesn't really hang out at Pats anymore.
Saying that we really moving away from Psych Awakens Tarot.
Why are you?
I said that.
Yep.
You said that.
Why are you?
Okay.
Yeah. It's okay. It's okay anymore. Remember that? So when you up here putting me on blast,
remember what you said. You're fucking stupid. Motherfucker.
The whole chatting tomorrow is just about Canada Drive tomorrow. Stay tuned on Sandman's Pains.
No, he's not even that important. I just give the loudest
You were talking about how you were gonna remove yourself and not really hanging out over here
And I should stop complaining about the fact that I'm not allowed. I'll say the same thing. So why so what people say things
They say things and then they come back. It don't matter
The one thing I want him to say just stand on it. He's mad
He's not manning up on it.
He's not manning up on what he said,
but he's attacking you for what you said.
I get what you said.
Weird bitch, yo.
He's like kind of like.
All he's trying to say is, did you or did you not say it?
Man up about it.
That's all he want to know.
I said what I said, and then I said what he said.
OK, so lose.
OK, but yeah, you said so you said.
But I thought you were OK with that with being kicked,
because he was all cool in my chat, like, oh, this is fun.
You know, I want to make it like.
He was crying for like 30 minutes.
I'll say be to shut this thing up.
Actually, no, you came on and I stopped talking about it and you
talked about it for like three hours last night. Well, hell,
I was what I didn't see Alex for a while. So what's Alan Scott
knew? You just went on. Oh,
psyche, psyche, psyche. I'm in the show. I'm in the show. I'm
in the show. Haha. You heard my peeps. Yo, Sam and shut the
fuck up. And you see, you're lucky, even though live and
walking fucking asshole.
Yo psyche pack read me a car my boy
One of my boys died yesterday. If you haven't seen me come on hand the shooting and then what did you officer died?
I'm warning right now. I need a car boy. That's not the last fuck that faggot
Everything's being recorded motherfucker, and you're going to jail soon. So shut up. Keep saying God bless that I'm where the officer died
Everything you're saying is recorded home be remember that
Yo, let me get a cord Pat. Yeah, I got a car for this guy. Just said. Thank God a cop died
Mike on my panel
Wow, Alex, you know, so wait. Hi. I don't give a fuck with my copper not motherfucker
Easy just said thank God the cop died and I haven't I think I can't I'm saying that in the past when the
Diller remember Diller
from a long island ship easy said yet he actually posted about it easy actually posted about it
So the police I like the police
Hey, how are you doing here's acid trip? I'm doing fine. Thank you. I just come to say hello
It's my like second time so good to you. I was on panel with you one time, but you school I don't mind it
Oh, yeah. Hello. Nice to meet you again. I like your background lights up now. It's quite fun
Got the second the second longest panel I see up. It was like last time I saw it was like 60 something hours or 48 hours of some shit
Wow
Long he was talking about it or the criminal you guys. I gotta know who's talking right now
The following or the bed line
Tell me not go come on
You're just fucking my type and bin Laden's that's easy
I just woke up are you related? Okay, dude. Thank you. I don't associate with um with Alex. So I'm gonna I'm a drop down
You're bad from this community remember those stupid words yesterday on one this panel on Miguel this guy
Well, you think whatever you
This listen easy, I'm gonna give you the best advice if you can't take it
Because you did a lot of shit and you can't take nothing bro
You're breaking the number one rule. Don't ditch it up. You can't take it homie. Now get the fuck out of my face
by
drop
What happened David?
What happened? I trust will shut the fuck up
And why P.D. Yonkos FBI will be Alex
So enjoy it enjoy it shut the fuck up and enjoy your freedom
I got your name. I got your address. I can sue you. I can start charges. I can fucking get you fucking rated
I can get you a beat up. I can get you whatever. I got your address and your name
You want me to put a picture of you and your kid right now on the panel
No doxing Alex. No doxing Alex and I'm not even threatening about it
You know you're not supposed to do that on my show Alex. No doxing fucking yeah, I'm gonna shoot back. Yeah, I'm sorry
He's like I'm gonna shoot back. He's not associate. You know the whole community's not um not letting them up
Not letting them right not letting them do nothing, right?
Okay, what do you got? Oh, yeah. Hi, Tony. Oh, yeah, because Tony's saying hi to you from the chat
So yeah, I mean, it was like he's just he's just being really loud. I don't like him threatening on my show
It's like he wants to threaten he can do it a perfect personal message and stuff like that
They're not not like through a through through my show. Hi. Hi Raymond. I'm sorry. You asked your question Raymond
I can pull you a card, but
Alex, I did have a card for you. It was you didn't let me get really to get in get it in but it was the fool card
So I think he's starting a new journey. I think he's starting his new life, you know
So, you know, don't just don't be too mournful of
Mournful because you know, I believe the spirit goes on and I think he's okay. Okay, so how are we doing tonight?
Got a nice check. Oh, hey, and by the way, Spunky's channel is called hey, they're spunky like you can search at hey
They're spunky and I think she might be doing it live. So go say hi to her right now. It's a psyche senses regards
I'm sorry. We've heard from fobby this week. Well, we can see
Let's see. This is a
Six of swords. Okay
So yeah, I think this is a this is a victory for you. So I think yes. I think that would be a yes. It's a victory
Who does
Yeah, he's got the long hand. Yeah, he does
Okay, I'm sorry, I didn't mean I was joking, but yeah, I'm sorry
Yeah, you do look a little like maybe maybe
That's myself just now well
Yeah, lucky I think before I speak
Yeah, I can't even say that forget it. Okay
So what's up guys, let me see. Yo, I can't say what I want to say without doxing something by myself, you know what I'm saying?
But yeah, we look alike it can happen like that
Yeah, yo, you know many times I walk down the street and I get called John Billy Troy or some type of other name like that's not me
I'm like, oh, no, no, no wrong person guy. He's like yo, you just like him
Yeah, well, let me see. Oh, so it's I got a public safety message Los Angeles County
Oh, we am tsunami advisory from beaches ports and low-lying areas in the coast of Los Angeles County starting around July 30th
Strong currents and dangerous waves expected to be near coastal waters. This is
I got you with this Becky ready. I was just on a live with my boy Stephen King here the radar system up our earthquake happened in Russia
Which is affecting Hawaii and in California somewhat. Uh-huh. Yeah, so I mean, I don't think uh
Don't think that's gonna be a big deal like you know, it's like what you know, I think they're making it a bigger thing
I don't think there's gonna be a tsunami taking away. You know anything in redondo, so
Maybe there's gonna be a big maybe a couple big bigger waves
I don't know, but I don't think it's gonna be a big deal
They buy in the Hawaii news the Hawaii news says stay above the four
Anything that's above four stories get on a higher platform above five to six stories high
Mm-hmm
Yeah, I know well, I live on a second story of my apartment and so hopefully you know, I'll be okay
California or anything if you're not really on coastline level you're not really gonna affect it
But you're a couple blocks away from postline level so yeah
Yeah, well they're prayer for me that I'll be okay, you know everyone in Los Angeles actually let's hope that everyone's okay
Hi, Miss Patel. Hi, Barry blue midnight. Hi everybody. Hopefully you're having a great night. We have nobody as a modding thing
That is member
Let's see. Hey everybody nice to see everybody. We've had Jamie Nick Johnson slayered the Catzilla you me
Hey everybody
So do you see the body the the powerlifter I had earlier on the show easy and you see that guy?
I had a power. I was drunk. I had my own live on and then I made my wife, you know, we got busy and then we fell asleep. Yeah.
We had a guy named Daddy Bigness on today, he's a power lifter, I found on YouTube and he came over and said hi.
He's busy today, all systems going out.
He was a busy bunny today, he saw some power lifting.
He said no more Nick Johnson lifting up towers, we got the real one.
Hello.
Yeah, it was fun though. He liked the show and he said he'll be back on the show
I didn't want to see that
I thought I heard you when you started you said he's coming over your way shit
Yeah, oh, yeah, he said he was gonna yeah
I talked to him earlier on when he was on a doing a live and you know, I said he needs some more people in his chat
I think I think he and I think he could make some make some
New fans here. And so I invited him over and we we contacted me on snapchat and was like, okay
What time's your show and and he was here when I got here at 5 and 5 p.m.
So I'm gonna thank Andrew. That was awesome. Hopefully he comes back. He said he'll come back tomorrow. So
Maybe he'll he'll be a new part of the show. He can be our fitness fitness expert
Yeah
But yeah, good morning you too. I think she's Indian at Patel is Indian. I believe so are you in India?
It is my name is my name is Patel. Oh cool. So you're Indian. Are you are you Indian descent?
I was I was well my parents are I was born in London
The common last name. So yeah, all right, so I gotta be more than over there
It's like a Smith basically you know, Mr. Smith. It's like that. It's just exactly like that. It's like Bob is Bob is a common name
Yeah, in the Arab world. Yes the number one name
Yeah, well, my name was the number one name and my name is John, you know, that was
John is the number one name too. Yeah, that was a common name at one point, you know
Or now it's not it's not as popular now. They have these like, you know, Colton and things like that, but
You know, whose microphone is messed up. Maybe mine. I'm sorry. My my ears
I need to go and smoke this marijuana, so I just want to say thank you for letting me on your panel
It's always fun out there man. Hey, I like that. You do a thumbs up and it popped up. That's pretty cool
Oh, yeah, that's it. Oh, it does work. Does it that thing? Oh, yeah, there's this other shit. Have you seen that shit?
Oh, it works like you can do this shit, right? And something happens. Yeah
You have a new iPhone, it's a new iPhone
I think I think I don't know you can do some hard
I think you can do like that and some other good shit happens
That's some shit. I mean, I don't know you can't control up, but I need to go out and smoke some dough
You repeat do the pizza
Thank you for letting me up. I really appreciate it. Okay. You're welcome. We're talking to you. Have a nice day
I think that was cool. Thank you. Is that alright?
Yeah, there you go
Yeah, I'm sobering up right now from a damn hangover from earlier. I was drinking too much
Yeah, I didn't really drink that I do have one one drink
I think I have left and so I might drink that I have us I have a
Twisted tea left or not twisted tea. Yeah, I have one twisted tea. I think I think last night
I puked it right out, I was like, oh, I felt bad and hangover and still feeling it right now, I'm just, I'm just drinking my water right now.
I've been let me see how many I have. Oh, I have one left. Yeah, I'll drink my one left. I
Yeah, I've been sleeping a lot so it's like and then this weed just like it's like a really like sleepy weed
So it makes me so tired. So if I have a hit of it, I just like it's hard. Yeah, but from
Seren person over here and for some reason I just started late. We talked about smoke that weed. I've been like, I'm gonna sleep
I got a bag of it right here, but like I don't want to even smoke it
No, but my weed is pretty good. It was it's like dragon fruit acai flavor. I can find it
Oh, I use a really good soap to today. I got this new soap
It's called called obi-wa
Dr. Squash, no, no, no, it was it's like a I can get the box. It's a really good soap. It's like a
spiritual kind of soap. It has a prayer in it and stuff. Let me see. Here it is.
You have the prayer on the soap? It has one in the inside the soap. It says, I'll read it to you. I
brought it over here. It says, it says, it's called Obi-Way. It says, protection. It says, Lord God,
I pray for your protection as I begin this day. You are my hiding place and I
And under your wings, I can always find refuge.
Protect me from trouble wherever I go
and keep evil far from me.
And that's like the little prayer it came with.
It also came with like a little coin inside of it.
It's like there's a little cool, like a little coin.
It has the O-monet, that's the O-monet.
And I would do it like, it basically after you wash up
and the signs go away, you get imprinted.
It smells really good. It says yeah, it's like a imprinting. Uh-huh imprint it
Yeah, it smells so good. Yeah, it's just like it's really it's called OB
Yeah, has anybody heard of it or do you know where it's from I do to be right there
Okay, I don't know. It's I'm thinking either Africa or India
There's some kind of like you know herb or something like that, but it's pretty it works pretty good. I like it. Hey, Joe Shippley
Welcome Joe come on Joe, I'm right something heart is broken whose heart is broken why?
Someone's heart is broken. I don't know. Let's see. What does it say? It says midnight as to see their taints and leave here all by my lungs
Oh, Barry blue. Come on
Tell you
But I use my new vacuum cleaner I got this vacuum for like 30 bucks on
Timu and it works really good. It's like it's kind of like
Small tank, but it has a really powerful suction and it's like who sounds up to do I hold on
Yeah, I'm about to check it out right now, if it's me, I'm about to check the volume level.
I don't know.
Joe is heartbroken from Florida Diamond.
What did you see yesterday?
We had Florida Diamond and Otto coming up.
Yeah, I jumped up.
I jumped up.
Otto's voice is very annoying.
Very annoying.
I couldn't continue watching.
I jumped up.
I did my little thing.
It showed up.
And when I left, I tried to watch it a little more and I was like, I can't watch it.
Yeah, well auto is pretty entertaining like it was kind of funny funny guy, but it's like it's a doughy like
I don't know. He's got that noise to me. He's a do it
It was funny. Jamie. Jamie's cowboys enjoyed it. Yeah, it was pretty funny. Yeah, I do it too. I was fucking with you
So I'm the rooster though. I'm the fucking rooster
I'll lay your finger up a lip man. Hey over that lip don't look too good
Uh-oh, so nobody and Joe are fighting in the chat. Come on guys. Everyone get along hopefully
But uh, so I've been on tiktok recently
I'll go for nobody. I'll go for nobody. Nobody's gonna win that one
Have you ever been on tiktok easy?
Never
That's addicting. I don't know it's a god
I don't know. I just don't I I I see I see people like I was watching somebody show through and stuff like that
I just don't
It's more for kitting, for the kitting.
No, because it's 18 or over, like, you know, it's supposed to be for adults, you know.
I feel, but the feeling of it brings, like, a kid feeling to me. It's like, oh, you know,
I'm good. Well, it's just like a different, like, for doing readings and stuff like that,
like, you know, because you have a lot of traffic going, and I bet it's like people will,
like, scroll through if they're not interested, but then you can put up on the screen. I put,
like, I put, like, free tarot readings, ask your question on the screen, and then that's,
like, I started getting, like, a lot of, like, people staying in the room and asking questions
of people there's all it's all different but there are like some really hot guys on that website it's
crazy and uh they are I don't know it's pretty it's pretty sexy website I don't know but uh it is
a fun uh oh your kids are well it's like it's supposed to be 18 or over but I guess people
can like scroll through it but I guess I don't think they can chat until you're 18 or something like
Yeah, I didn't want to get on that too. Yeah, and then them Trump banned that shit. So that's definitely why I didn't take that shit
Well, it's actually but I'm already monetized on there try to go to TROB stream. What is TROB's who's TROB's?
But I'm already monetized on it. I already have a membership
You know that people can get and stuff like that. So it's pretty cool. I don't know midnight. That's a very strange question. Come on
They don't ask for ID. Well, they did ask for my ID when I when I started my channel
They need before broadcasting. I needed to send my ID to prove I was 18 at least 18. And so I
Sent mine. I guess some people can use somebody else's account though, but
Right. Yeah, yeah, anybody can send in like grab the brother's idea or some shapes take a picture
Yeah
Yeah. Oh, yeah, the world's changed nowadays, but in that and everyone's on everyone's on camera nowadays, too
You wouldn't like it. It's all about politics and religious debates
Yeah, sometimes they're more strict over there. I heard that like any little thing like you see how you like your
questions of how you offer YouTube
Yeah, I can't. Oh, yeah
If I even smoke a cigarette or like blowout smoke or anything it gets restricted immediately
It gets like restricted like, you know
Yeah, and it's like it happens like instantly
It's like it's like they have this AI like either the AI or they have people in the room watching or something like that
They do it instantly because also on cake if you mess with cake like I watch a lot of kick lately
I'll be over there
Yeah, I think I got probably a kicked off of kick because of like
I was dual streaming, but then it's like, yeah, so I was like smoking on kick and
Don't know if I rumble I had a rumble I was using to but I stopped but it's like now that looks like that counts disappeared
But my rumble is already syndicated by tripkick. They syndicate me and beta and like Q and some other people on rumble
So they have like shows that like I delete are over there, but not under my you know identity. So
So that's pretty good so I can have like an archive of shows that I don't necessarily have to
be responsible for so
But I don't know I hopefully it won't they won't get a they count deleted because there is like probably
Four bombs on some of those shows, so they would have to delete them down their own and watch the whole show and make sure
so
Who has the who do you think has the high-pitched voice or whatever West Coast right? I don't know of me
I'm sorry if I'm a little bit confused. I sound very tired. I'm not even loud
Hey, look at this SD Monstro the hey, how are you doing? I haven't seen you for a lot while come on up if you
Want to I'll put the link up again
And Monstro is like the Mexican wrestler character. I haven't seen you for a long time. Nice to see you
We're just having a little let me see we're seven little little
Midnight chat is midnight in Los Angeles exactly midnight in Los Angeles July 30th. We're almost out of the month
Gonna have August
So hopefully you guys are doing good. Let me see. I'll pin. I'll try to pin my link
I don't know how much longer I'll be on tonight. Maybe like just maybe maybe an hour longer or something if I
I'll see
Stopped out. I must step down. Let's see it up as team my stroll as the maestro come appears for psyche
Yeah, come on up if you want to support later
Later
Nice talking to you. Okay, so there was my
I'm trying to pin the link real quick you see view channel
Yeah, luckily um Aldi did porn bomb me earlier, you know, it's kind of terrible
I didn't want to see that
and
I apologize guys that he did porn bomb and I had to delete the second show of the day
But
Hey, Joe, how's everybody so the link is pinned? I'm doing another free night tonight just to some
Little bit down lately a little bit a little bit more tired. Hopefully tomorrow will be a good day
How is everybody doing okay got some cat food coming tomorrow
Let's see did I ever yeah, I have a bidet. I have like one of those but it's one of those
Ones that I installed myself, you know, this panel is free Joe. Yep. Okay. We have Monstro here
Yo, hey, what's up psyche? How have you been good? Can you hear me? Yeah, you fine? Okay?
I'm here in LA right now. Oh, you are me too. Well, you know, I'm in LA
I'm in Englewood
You are okay. We're not too far. I'm in Redondo Beach. And so, uh, you know Englewood's probably about half hour
Half hour away. Nice. What are you doing over here? I?
Just left a concert at the forum
What'd you see?
Lady Gaga. Oh
Cool
That sounds like a lot of fun. How was the show? It was fun my cousin. She wanted to see her
So I took her about I got her ticket
Oh, wow, how nice of you your cousin. Yeah, what a lucky cousin, you know
I got a ticket and I recorded some of it. I'm an upload it on my YouTube channel, but I recorded some of the show
cool
Yeah, it's been quite a while. Yeah, it's been a while. You know, I saw you alive. I just wanted to say what's up
Yeah
We had a power lifter on earlier kind of I kind of thought about you a little bit like I was like
Oh everyone I had that Mexican wrestler on I had some all kinds of athletes on my show at one point
But you know the shows kind of got a little bit different
But I don't know if I was monetized when I first met you but I've been monetized for several months now
It's like it's I got monetized in April and the show's doing pretty well. I have a lot of other
little ways that I
make money here too, and so it's worked out pretty well.
Let's do it. I might come up later. Just right now I'm driving, so I can't come up and drive. You know, it's kind of dangerous.
No problem.
I'm driving back home. I'm driving back to San Diego.
Oh, you're driving to San Diego now?
Yeah, because the show's over, so I'm driving back home.
Well, actually in December I went to King Diamond in San Diego
I had my friend I had a friend named hell Walker and he came in peace from San Diego
He picked me up and he drove me down there and it was King Diamond. It was actually
VIP so we got to get a picture taken with them and got like a bag a bag of merchandise and
It was pretty cool. So I got to go to San Diego for a little bit last year, but
I know that you're in the California area
Yeah, I'm right in LA. Yeah, I'm right in LA and Redondo. So, you know, not far from Inglewood and
Hey, listen, I want to thank you. I want to thank you for allowing me to join your podcast when I was shit-faced drunk
Yeah, no problem. No problem. You're an entertaining guest. I thought it was pretty funny and yeah
I know I said a lot of things that I regret because
Because when I drink I go haywire
Well, that's okay. That's okay. You didn't say anything that bad. I don't think, you know
I think you might have like maybe I think you might have thrown up one time and
Me doing a lot of crazy things
Yeah, I've seen you on other shows too, you know pop up on some other shows
I forgot who's but you know either Samans or
Or somebody else's but yeah, I've seen you pop a few other shows and
You know, I'm a I kind of have established myself in the panel verse a little bit now. So
So I'm sure you know who captain content is right
Yeah, cuz he dated a lease. I'm aware of him a little bit. Yeah
well, that's how he kind of
he helped me grow like with the
content and the
He helped me get viewers and everything cuz I stream your friends with them, right? Yeah, you are friends with them
Yeah, I heard a couple stories not anymore not anymore because uh
Well, the story was is that we were supposed to meet up and stream in LA and he
He flaked on me, right and
That day I was supposed to meet up with him in the stream. He he ghosted me
He ignored my phone calls and that same night is when he met up with a lisa
Oh, yeah, but instead of saying hey, I can't make it. He just just didn't respond on my phone call
Well, uh, she might have that effect on some guys, you know, I don't know. She I think
like, if it's even at her, he probably wasn't thinking about many other things. She is,
uh, well, I, you know, you know, I like her a lot. I haven't talked to her or been on
her show in a few weeks, though. Have you heard of a summer page nine? No, what's that?
Would you play that video? I don't know they clipped they clipped me in that video, and I'm in it. It's like a Alisa
Singing I'm your captain now. Have you heard of that song? Yeah
Is it hers or is it somebody else's because my ma DM he said hey you're in that music video
I'm like what music video of Alisa singing. I'm your captain now, and he sent me the link
I think I'm in like in the beginning of it
Which is is it was a her video where she's like dancing and singing in it like a good man
Yeah, she's it's her song and she's singing and then I'm in the video. It's when I slapped captain in the face
Okay
So that's yeah, yeah, that is cool. There are a lot of views
I never met her. No, I'm trying to
I'm trying to stay away from the
community because
It's really toxic and I've been
Well, she's not an IP to I mean she was an IP to but she's not and she I think she got kicked out of IP to or something
So she's pretty much her own
her own person but uh and she doesn't really care for like a lot of IP to people I mean she does mess with some of them but
She doesn't like that too much of the sexual sense of humor. I don't think
No, but the thing with ip2, you know, you you say you're you're not there anymore, but they're they stick with you
You say no, I'm not no longer involved, but they
Yeah, cuz it's the audience it's the audience right it's the audience, but I don't get a lot of ip2 people anymore
We have someone named desk. Oh destiny's here. Hold on destiny. Yeah. Hello
Hello guys, how are you?
Good. How are you destiny? I'm good. Hello. Say hi to Bonstro. This is destiny and the destiny is in Brazil, correct?
I'm good thanks. How are you? Good. Good. It's been a little bit. I'm good. Yes. Yes.
Uh, don't drink and drive if you're drinking. I'm just drinking some setup. I
Know
We're talking about a Lisa Jordana. Do you know who that is?
No, no
Sorry, she's a streamer a streamer and she's kind of a popular IRL streamer
That I followed but uh
So how's your girlfriend?
She's good. Thanks. She's in
She's actually working tonight. Unfortunately, she she
She wants to come over
And I and I'm just bored, you know
You're bored tonight. Yeah
You're bored. We're welcome to the conversation because we're bored as well
Thank you
Yeah, do you like me without my beard? I shaved my beard a little bit. It's growing back. Oh, yeah, man
You know, you look younger. That's a good idea to shave your beard. Yeah
It gets kind of like, you know, I got it. I got a new electric razor. So I'm able to shave a little bit better now
Yeah, man, you look good man. Keep it shaved. Thank you. And I got my these are reading glasses
I have to wear reading glasses now my because my eyes have gone bad trying to read the stream yard and so
Have I have some Jeffrey Dahmer style ones. I don't know where they are around here someplace, but yeah
I just got those the pretty cool. Hey sake, you know, I noticed that your channel has grown since I was last joined your live
Yeah, congrats man congrats on the cloud and you deserve it
Thank you very much. Yeah, I think I might like kind of slow down a little bit, but I'm a 2600
Subscribers and I have like, you know, there's like 28 people here now
I sometimes between like 20 and 60 people sometimes a little bit more, but I might be shadow band a little bit
I don't know. I have a lot of porn bombers a lot of bad language and racial language on the show sometimes, but
No, you're good man. The last time I joined you had less followers and now it looks like you're on the come-up
Yeah
Like that. You like that. That's my
The kitty cat. Yep, I got the cats around the cat cats around me. Yeah, no, there's Lola. Hi, babe
The cats around it's Lola miss Lola. She's kind of dark in here. Yep
Talking about everybody show. I was watching your show and there was this older Mexican gentleman that joined
Hmm auto and auto
Yeah, and then I noticed Joe made a comment. He said that that was my dad. Oh
Joe
Remember that from last night. Yeah
Yeah, so I was watching and I noticed he made that comment. So
Joe if you're watching you want to come up and defend yourself because I'm gonna call you out. No
Yeah, I think it was a joke. I think he was joking about but yeah
That was auto and then auto auto is now in love with 30 diamond though
You know, so I don't know if you know who flirty diamond is but you know, yeah
Yeah, I defended I defended her before because people are making fun of her
because they were calling her a sushi
I don't want you guys to get me wrong but
I just want to know that if you were
in person like in the house
or in person that you guys would do the same
in the face of the person you know like
You know, you would be so brave to tell them everything that we say online, because I know sometimes I talk a lot of shit,
but sometimes I talk facts, you know, what I think.
I'm a very spontaneous person. I speak my mind.
I don't care what people say, what they think.
And I know to I know to be cautious to be to be careful
When I say some things but
Would you ever
Stop and think that would I do that in person? You know because this is very dangerous, you know
I understand what you're saying, but this is mainly for content, so when we talk to other people and we want to fight each other, it's mainly for the content.
Yeah, I don't think it too seriously, but I am more like you know on if I'm on camera
If I have my show going I'm more willing to talk to people on the outside
Like I'm very like extroverted now where I was introverted before if I'm on the show
And so yeah, you the show does make a difference. I would say
But Joe Joe on the other hand he's on his name is no show Joe because Hector wanted to fight him at the park
And it was all on live stream and Joe never showed up so his name officially now is no show Joe
One thing that we need to understand that people they are not obligated
They're they're not they don't need to show themselves if they want to they don't want you
I know that a lot of people, they hate me on the internet because I speak my mind,
sometimes I am, I confess that I am a bit sometimes, I insult people, I'm very rude,
but sometimes I'm a very nice person, I'm not like that in real life, you know,
and the people normally know you in person.
So, they make the wrong conclusion about you, you know, and so they think that you are the
person that you are telling that you are online.
Of course, this express a lot of who you are, your emotions, your personality and everything,
This is not actually who you are because I don't know why but in person
I'm a very nice sweet person. Everybody likes me, but when I came online
Everybody attacks me for no reason. That's why I try to defend myself
That's what I try to talk, but sometimes I know I am wrong. I know I am guilty, you know
I know the problem is with me
I know to recognize when the problem with is with me. This is the first step
You need to recognize that you are wrong first right well people are gonna misjudge you online
Just because they don't know you and so it's like you'll have a different personality online sometimes
But I'm sure if people know you in real life
It'll be better like it'll get along better in real life than you will on online because people are just like to fight
They're just looking for fights here sometimes right
Exactly exactly yes
Sorry, I was saying hi page in the chat go ahead
No, go ahead. Go ahead. You can try to say how to page in the chat. Just say I had a page in the chat my homegirl
Sir, yes
How can I leave the gates closed?
All right, thank you
Hi Lola, my cat Lola is climbing all over me.
Yeah well it's just important to know that it's like online is kind of like, it's not like the same as real life and you know it is, it's very similar and there's you know it is real people but it's like everybody's gonna be a little bit different on their way to present themselves on you know on camera on a show from an audience in regular life right?
I was third row behind the front of the stage at the Gaga concert with my cousin.
Well, I got some really good video of her third row right behind the front stage
I'm pretty jealous. I would love to see a lady gaga concert. I even know
Those are thousand dollar ticket the wrong thousand dollars per seat
Man, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. This is very personal
Individual it's very personal, but
I don't like her. She was in my country like this month. And I don't really like this American
artist that they're big, you know, because I know what is behind the American industry.
We need to find it
No, yes, but if you like it if you like it, I have no problem with it
You can like whatever you want to you. I don't really care, you know, but I
Don't care because there's a lot of
They said they tell that
They tell that it's conspiracy theory or something like that, but there's a lot of
A lot of strange things happening out in their shows, in their music and messages and everything, you know.
If you study it just like myself, because I was in college and I studied about history and theology and pagan, pagan religion, and ...
This is really creepy man, people think that this, in our modern world, this doesn't exist anymore, but it really does.
If you look around the world, we have pagan cyborgs symbols all around the world, even in Vatican, all around the world.
You know
No, Joe, I know this is this is a boring conversation because
That's the main reason that people don't like me because I like to just talk about this stuff
You know, okay, you're entitled to your opinion. That's fine. I got no response
Thank you. Yeah, thank you
Expand express yourself. Yeah, it's like I yeah
my cousin loves her so
I support, it was her birthday, so I got her tickets to the Gaga show.
That's it, you're an awesome cousin, and I wish I had a cousin that would take me to the concert.
So you're telling me you're painting, if you don't like an artist, that's fine.
You can go ahead and say whatever you'd like.
Yes.
Exactly. My brother, David, he was last year in the show of Maier Curry and in my country
Man, I can't tell you that. You know what I like? You think that I am a very eccentric
and weird right now. You know what I really like? Cisco was 11. Cisco was a child. I like
I like classical music, this is what I really enjoy, this is what I really like, for real, for real, it doesn't mean, it doesn't mean that I don't like rap, I like rap, trap, drill, UK drill, Brazilian drill, French drill, whatever, trance music,
I like all Germanists, a lot of Germanists of music, but my favorite is classical music and
you know that's why I say that looks can be deceiving, you know.
Okay, you like music, can you sing?
No, I actually can't sing you know, I can't sing but I
But I really enjoyed this genre of music since I was a child.
That's good. Well, yeah, you come like whatever you'd like. There's no...
Right, we're not judging you for it, but yeah.
Yeah, we're not judging you.
I don't know what to say almost
Hold on, there's a checkpoint up ahead of police officers
for people who are drinking and driving
Hopefully, are you good?
I'm good, I haven't been drinking
You hear my cat purring? He's one of the covers purring with me
My cat tricks
Everybody is different, it's subjective
Everybody is different
Yeah, you can like whatever you'd like you do who do you want?
Yes, here the cat purring
Oh, I can't wait to get to my cat at home. I have a cat myself
His name is Troy one of these days he'll pop up on stream
cool
Yeah, how many cats do you have psyche? I have five cats
oh nice yeah I haven't seen one of them in a while yeah I basically have four
because like one of them is like always you know it's on this out on the streets
and then comes back once in a while but four of them are always in the house
usually it's probably under that blanket with one of them this is tricks hi
tricks I don't know if you can hear him but he's purring right now just hugging
me so nice to sleep with a kitty
That's cool. I love animals
Right now and Troy is like the world to me. Yeah, that night I sleep with him. He curls with me in bed
He's like my other blanket
That's really cool. Yeah
They have a great frequency vibration, you know
Yeah
Go ahead. Were you gonna say something you can go ahead and say it. No, I just say that I like cats, but I
I wish I had one but I
gave it to my mom
You know, but I really like her and
I think as they're very independent, you know, but I really like them, you know.
Yeah, well, I can't serve my life. They're like my kids, so...
Hey, Saki, if you don't mind me asking, what's your content about now? Is this still about...?
You know people content. Oh, I do tarot readings and like also like I just have like people come up on panel and
There's like a lot of controversy. There's a lot of interesting guests. There's I had a had actually a power lifter on today
So I'm trying to find different guests from around YouTube to bring on and like, you know, but you know sometimes beat is here
You know talking some shit the other people there's always like a lot of shit talking and like you know, there's I don't know
It's just whoever it's just you never know what's gonna happen on my show. It's always like a
It's a surprise even for me. Oh, that's cool. Who's in chat right now?
Let me have a look. Okay, so in chat we have
Let's see mama Maria with us close right. We have Joe Shippley's in chat Joe Shippley come on up
He invited he told you to come up. Jamie's Cowboys
Devil eyes Felipe. Halo. Yeah, I think Jamie's Cowboys is here yet. Jamie's Cowboys
VB
Stop furry page. Hi furry page West Coast, right? Yeah, it's just like a lot of people. There's 28 people in chat
I don't know
Come on guys, feel free to come up on panel the panel is open right now. I'm say hi to a monster
Yeah, you have Joe has a crush on be that well, that's okay
Come on up Joe if you want if you want to okay? What's up everyone as the monster here?
I love all of you. I'm here chatting with my friend psyche and we're just having a good time
Yeah, it's nice my well, yeah
Hey man, thanks for letting me on. I need no problem to talk to you after this long a concert
No problem over you have a good time. I just dropped off my cousin and now I'm driving back home to San Diego
so
So kind of lonely, you know, just over this long drive. It's a two-hour drive. I'm in LA right now
Yeah, I'm back south and I saw that you were alive. So I'm decided to join
Yeah, this is like a little bit of a drive if you drive past you drive past some military bases, right? Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I remember that that driving just hitting the South freeway, so
But I'd give you some company
sailing
Yeah, if anyone wants to come up. So so spunky is pretty hot. So how is spunky showed the spunky? Maybe the new spot
Well, maybe but hopefully that she had a good show and I think that we don't it's like not necessarily a new spot
It's just like another spot. We were because there's too much to forever one person to like, you know
How hosts a chat so it's like it's always better to have like a lot more people, right?
So yeah, don't be shy come up and talk to us. Yeah, there's no competition. It's spunky
So yes, yes, yes, come up come up and talk to them
Please and and I just want to say one thing that I
Riddle I really enjoy
Psycho how do you say your name and cycle cycle psyche like? Oh, sorry psyche. I
Really really enjoy when you are reading
You make me relax and fall asleep, you know, oh you like what I read. Okay. Well, I'll do some more reading later
You know, I like to read about interesting things
So
You know people to sleep, but that's a good thing
Thank you. I really appreciate it
I have to go and I wish you guys a good night and take care destiny
Have a great night. Thank you. You too. Thank you for having me. Thank you so much. Bye. Bye
Yeah, she's nice
Oh, this candle so cuddly he's like he like wants to come under the covers and then once I'm under the covers
He's like he like puts his paws over my arm and it's just like cuddling up to me. He's so sweet
Oh, I'm in heaven
Hey sakey have a question
Yeah. Hey, I noticed when I was last on your live, you know, I got really drunk and I was like taking off my clothes. I
Don't know if you took to me. I think you might have taken off your shirt at my request, but yeah, because one of my moderators
Messaged me and told me and there's like clips of me
He showed me one of the clips of me like
Taking off my shirt
Yeah, I think I was asking you to flex and you like eventually did flex that's true
That's true. I remember that I need to drink more. I need to drink more
I need to drink more and then you would drink more and then you flex
Okay, good because the guest today flexed he had no problem doing it
So it's like I don't think there's a big problem with flexing. I don't think it's like that
that
And then I drink when I drink too much I get you know, I don't remember because I get blacked out drunk
That's the bad thing about me
Well, you're a good sport. You're a good sport. Here I am.
Let's see
You know cuz once you go live and then you know the clips they stay out there forever
Yeah, I'm sure there's clips of me too. So, you know, I've been I have been put several times by like clip clip talk and trip kick and
You know, but I don't mind. It's just like usually it's funny
I also have had cartoons made of me and so and I think they're pretty funny. So I don't mind
I'm good with the being clipped and all that kind of stuff. Oh
Just
Getting warm. Oh
Okay, guys. Well, I don't know. He's taking off
I'm getting tired though. I think I might go to sleep, but maybe I'll be back, but I love you guys